<resources>
    <string name="app_name">moviecatalog1</string>

    <string-array name="title">
        <item>Aquaman</item>
        <item>Avengers: Infinity War</item>
        <item>Bird Box</item>
        <item>Bumblebee </item>
        <item>Deadpool 2</item>
        <item>How to Train Your Dragon: The Hidden World</item>
        <item>Dragon Ball Super: Broly </item>
        <item>Ant-Man and the Wasp </item>
        <item>Spider-Man: Into the Spider-Verse</item>
        <item>venom</item>
    </string-array>

    <array name="image">
        <item>@drawable/poster_aquaman</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_avengerinfinity</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_birdbox</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_bumblebee</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_deadpooll</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_dragon</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_dragonball</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_antman</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_spiderman</item>
        <item>@drawable/poster_venom</item>

    </array>


    <string-array name="realese">
        <item>December 21, 2018</item>
        <item>April 27,2019</item>
        <item>November 12, 2018</item>
        <item>December 21, 2018</item>
        <item>May 10, 2018</item>
        <item>January 3, 2019</item>
        <item>December 14, 2018</item>
        <item>July 6, 2018</item>
        <item>December 14,2018</item>
        <item>October 5, 2018</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="info">
        <item>Once home to the most advanced civilization on Earth, Atlantis is now an underwater kingdom ruled by the power-hungry King Orm. With a vast army at his disposal, Orm plans to conquer the remaining oceanic people and then the surface world. Standing in his way is Arthur Curry, Orms half-human, half-Atlantean brother and true heir to the throne.</item>
        <item>As the Avengers and their allies have continued to protect the world from threats too large for any one hero to handle, a new danger has emerged from the cosmic shadows: Thanos. A despot of intergalactic infamy, his goal is to collect all six Infinity Stones, artifacts of unimaginable power, and use them to inflict his twisted will on all of reality. Everything the Avengers have fought for has led up to this moment - the fate of Earth and existence itself has never been more uncertain.</item>
        <item>Five years after an ominous unseen presence drives most of society to suicide, a survivor and her two children make a desperate bid to reach safety.</item>
        <item>On the run in the year 1987, Bumblebee finds refuge in a junkyard in a small Californian beach town. Charlie, on the cusp of turning 18 and trying to find her place in the world, discovers Bumblebee, battle-scarred and broken. When Charlie revives him, she quickly learns this is no ordinary yellow VW bug.</item>
        <item>Wisecracking mercenary Deadpool battles the evil and powerful Cable and other bad guys to save a boys life.</item>
        <item>As Hiccup fulfills his dream of creating a peaceful dragon utopia, Toothless’ discovery of an untamed, elusive mate draws the Night Fury away. When danger mounts at home and Hiccup’s reign as village chief is tested, both dragon and rider must make impossible decisions to save their kind.</item>
        <item>Earth is peaceful following the Tournament of Power. Realizing that the universes still hold many more strong people yet to see, Goku spends all his days training to reach even greater heights. Then one day, Goku and Vegeta are faced by a Saiyan called
            Broly who they never seen before. The Saiyans were supposed to have been almost completely wiped out in the destruction of Planet Vegeta, so whats this one doing on Earth? This encounter between the three Saiyans who have followed completely different destinies turns into a stupendous battle, with even Frieza (back from Hell) getting caught up in the mix.</item>
        <item>ust when his time under house arrest is about to end, Scott Lang once again puts his freedom at risk to help Hope van Dyne and Dr. Hank Pym dive into the quantum realm and try to accomplish, against time and any chance of success, a very dangerous rescue mission.</item>
        <item>Miles Morales is juggling his life between being a high school student and being a spider-man. When Wilson "Kingpin" Fisk uses a super collider, others from across the Spider-Verse are transported to this dimension.</item>
        <item>Investigative journalist Eddie Brock attempts a comeback following a scandal, but accidentally becomes the host of Venom, a violent, super powerful alien symbiote. Soon, he must rely on his newfound powers to protect the world from a shadowy organization looking for a symbiote of their own.</item>
    </string-array>




</resources>
